healthsbody.com 2010-11-23

# Privacy Policy - Health Body

Security

HealthsBody.Com has security measures in place to help protect against the loss, misuse and/or unauthorized alteration of the information under our control. You are the only user authorized to update your profile, unless you provide your password information to another party. HealthsBody.Com helps protect your identifying information with both online and offline security, including firewalls, passwords, security certificates, and restricted physical access to the server where your information is stored.

Identifying Information

To protect the privacy of our users, HealthsBody.Com does not sell, share, or rent identifying information with third parties, such as advertisers or promotional partners unless the user chooses to do so by "opting in" to promotional deals. Any subsequent interaction with these third parties will be governed by the privacy policy of the third party. Therefore, you decide if and with whom HealthsBody.Com shares your identifying information.

Aggregate Data

We gather aggregate data about the types of loan searches completed and the services utilized. This information does not contain any identifying information. This data is collected by HealthsBody.Com for internal purposes so that we can improve our offering; it may also be disclosed to third parties such as advertisers, partners, and content providers.

Passive Information Collection

HealthsBody.Com uses cookies to provide convenience and better service on the site. By setting a cookie on your computer, the site eliminates the need for you to log in with a username and a password more than once in a visit, thereby saving you time while on our site. This passive information may be combined with your other information for purposes such as testing and improving your experience at our site and the compilation of broad aggregate demographic data and related usage information.

Acceptance of Terms/Changes to Privacy Policy

Your use of this site indicates an acceptance of the terms of the Privacy Policy. HealthsBody.Com reserves the right to update or amend this policy at any time.

Disclaimer

Although our site strives to provide accurate information and advice, HealthsBody.Com does not guarantee the accuracy, reliability or completeness of any of the information provided on this site, including loan information, interest rates, and borrower benefits. 

Links to Other Sites

This site contains links to other sites. The links are provided for your convenience only. Please note that HealthsBody.Com does not have any control over the information, products, services or policies of third-party companies accessible through our site. We encourage users to read the privacy policy of each site they visit when they leave our site.
